INFO:



Dmytro HoiPython Developer

E-mail: me@dmytrohoi.com
LinkedIn: dmytrohoi
Telegram: @dmytrohoi
Site: dmytrohoi.com

SUMMARY:

I have been programming in Python for over two years. I worked on the following projects: the custom test framework on Python based on Appium for medical embedded project (real medical device); big Telegram bots; sites parsing scripts on Python/JS with Regex; console scripts on .sh (site deploying, environment setup and etc); contribution to open-source projects on GitHub (python-telegram-bot, aiogram); plugins and a plugin loader for the famous game; personal site based on ReactJS.

My personal projects are collected in dmytrohoi.com/#projects.

Additional programming languages are: Javascript, sh, Ruby and Go (learning in progress). I finished studying Systems Analysis, including machine learning.

SKILLS:

- Languages: Python, JavaScript, Ruby, sh, Go (learning in progress).
- Libraries/Frameworks: pytest, appium, python-telegram-bot/aiogram, Django, Flask, SQLAlchemy/Gino, requests, tkinter, Jupyter, Pelican
- IDE/Code Editors: VSCode**, VIM
- English-level: Intermediate
- OS: Ubuntu, Arch, Windows
- Tools: Git, SVN, adb, cron, Docker, venv/pipenv
- Other: zsh, HTML/CSS, SQL, Regex, GitHub, sr.ht

Details on my site: dmytrohoi.com

ADDITIONALS SKILLS:

- Initiative and pro-active
- Public speaking skill
- Process automation loving
- Writing articles (<u>habr.com/users/dmytrohoi</u> | <u>dev.to/dmytrohoi</u> | <u>higaindev.ml</u>)
- SMM, PR, Poems writing

PERSONAL PROJECTS:

- pelican-gsb a tool for quickly building Pelican-based websites (PvPI)
- <u>hi gain dev</u> personal programming blog
- <u>freelancehunt-api</u> framework for public API (<u>PyPI</u>)
- <u>pyplugins</u> plugin loader for the famous game (2 plugins based on it)
- freelance projects: Telegram Bots and programs with a GUI

WORK EXPERIENCE:

Company: GlobalLogic

Position: Python Developer in Test / AQA (05/2019 - now)

Info: Implementation of the custom test framework for the embedded device on Android

Pie (using Python, Appium, ADB, and pytest)

Company: Microbilt

Position: Site Scraping Script Developer (07/2018 - 05/2019)

Info: programming with Regex and SQL, Python and Javascript automation scripting

Company: National University of Radioelectronics

Position: Senior Assistant (06/2016 - 05/2017)

Info: Quality Assurance Department. ISO 9001 certification. Creation and updating of an

internal quality assurance system.

EDUCATION:



<u>Kharkiv National University of</u> <u>Radioelectronics</u>

- Bachelor (2014 2018) Electronics - "Electronics devices and systems"
- Master (2018 2019)
 System Analysis "Consolidated information"

DMYTRO HOI / Sep 2020 2/2

E-mail: me@dmytrohoi.com | LinkedIn: dmytrohoi | Site: dmytrohoi.com | Site: dmytrohoi.com | Site: <a href="meddmytrohoi